foreign  Cyrus are you feeling okay baby you  haven't even opened your Benta box yet  you know I woke up extra early this  morning to make it special  I'm sorry Trevor I know you did I guess  I just have a lot of smelly crap on my  mind right now  would you like to talk about it dear I  will always be here if you need me  I know you are Trevor I know you are but  this is something I have to deal with on  my own Cyrus am I not closer to you than  anyone else  of course you are you're my best friend  and and so much more  I am  so we can fix it  the school dances tonight and the week  after that we'll be graduation  everyone's families are surely going to  be there  is that it  well don't you feel a little embarrassed  knowing that your parents won't be there  to cheer for you like the other kids  oh Trevor I'm sorry I didn't mean no  you're right after all it is hard every  day when I see the other kids getting  picked up by their mummies and daddies I  wouldn't like it hurts  but I manage I find ways to manage in  this cruel Dark World  mostly by acting kind of gay  I guess we were a lot more similar than  I thought  when I was still [ __ ] in diapers my  dad took me on trips outside of the  country  oftentimes I would see things that I  shouldn't have things that I knew would  tear my own family apart if the secrets  got out  I caught my dad having butt sex with the  evil Dr Robotnik  instead of killing me they decided to  keep me quiet with the promise of 30  happy meals a day  but of course my dad was still married  to my mum and jealousy overtook Robotnik  I'm so angry  what was that get down [ __ ]  damn it Robotnik what the [ __ ] are you  doing here I told you we'd pick on the  weekends [ __ ] you [ __ ] this will  teach you for playing with a man's heart  what are you saying the only thing I  played with was a man's boss  foreign  wife she's gone what have you done  no I didn't mean to I was only trying to  scare her away  your roundness we have to get out of  here the neighbors are surely calling  the police  then we have to make like black people  with another person's TV and get out of  here dingo help me get this guy in the  trunk and change my adult diaper sleep  you go around the house and clear the  place out no survivors  foreign  [Music]  it doesn't have to be like this  give yourself up and Robotnik may just  force you to be his sex slave instead  it's enough or nothing  my ah  I knew it with how ugly your debt was I  knew there had to be an equally ugly  baby damn it he's fast  this baby must have gotten one too many  cookies out of the jar tonight  [Music]  you won't get away with this robotic my  son will find me by following the fumes  of my beefy yellow ass and then he will  rape you and maybe he'll rape me also  because I beat him regularly with a belt  but mostly you  close it  I guess in a way I can feel what you're  going through my parents were also tell  by Robotnik and his dastardly guns  before my very eyes  hey I have an idea why don't we be the  ones to kill Robotnik and his little  [ __ ] ourselves  the reason we couldn't stop what  happened back then was because we were  still hooping in dirty diapers  we aren't those fat babies anymore  Trevor so let's go make it happen you  and me  tonight while everyone else is  distracted with the dance we'll plot Our  Revenge scheme and the music at the  dance will cover up his screams of Agony  like and Twilight when the vampires had  to play baseball during thunderstorms  that's enough out of you  if the great Sonic the Hedgehog himself  couldn't finish off Dr Robotnik for good  what chance do we have I think it's  about time you come to term with it  Cyrus what happened to all those years  ago cannot be undone  but if we can't send Robotnik and his  goons to their graves we'll all be  happier you and I can move on with our  lives we can buy a house in the  countryside and then quiet I don't want  to hear anymore until the dance let's  just spend these few hours happy in  peace because the minute we graduate  everything is going to change forever  you feel it too don't you the drive  preventions itching its way across your  sweaty unshaven balls  when you finally come to your senses  come find me I'll be on the School  rooftop getting ready  fine [ __ ] off then I still get your  Japanese Bento  [Music]  is it my turn yet for the 11th time yes  throw down your cards for a chaotic  Showdown  what are you talking about I only asked  once you were sitting there doing  nothing for five minutes  and whose fault is that  obviously it's yours you goofball don't  you know it's common courtesy to  announce the end of your turn when  you're done  not if you're trying to stall so the  time could run out dingo that's cheating  new uh this is  damnit thing face give me back my Max or  [Music]  dingo what the hell that was Max the  legendary champion it cost me 90 bucks  on Amazon  guess you should have used eBay instead  [ __ ]  huh  hey sleet don't you think the Keebler  dude is kind of hot  Kibler dude you mean that creepy looking  elf [ __ ] on the cookie package  I mean he's not that bad looking for a  [ __ ] I guess slap on a big ass pair of  honk and it's and I'd probably type it  you can miss me with the chip midgets  are half the size of normal people so  mathematically speaking he's at least 50  but crack and cheeks now forgive my  crude language sleet but Keebler dudes  got a booty  Bingo dingo are you going we're in the  middle of an epic showdown  I can't not while he's still out there  the Keebler Elf no not him while he is  also technically out there making  cookies with his KF boyfriend in the  woods somewhere I speak of somebody else  somebody dangerous the boy who lived  sleet there's something I have to tell  you a long time ago Robotnik sent me on  a mission in the dead of night I didn't  know what I was meant to do but I knew  there was no turning back  I received a secret call from our Master  he was being attacked after I changed  out of the Underpants I pooped in the  previous night I I killed a boy's  parents sleet he was no older than three  and yet I took What mattered most in the  world from him his mommy and daddy  foreign  such as the life of a bounty hunter  dingo it's our job to carry out the  mission  no matter who it affects in the end  you don't get it [ __ ] it's probably  because you're gay  Dinko I'm not gay  oh my mistake I was accidentally talking  about myself okay wait you're gay  oh I'm loser say what what dammit  he's still alive growing stronger like  ninja eventually he's going to want  revenge against my orange crayon colored  as and I don't know if I'm going to be  strong enough to beat him  it seems to me that a little training is  in order sleep go get me my three pound  dung Bells this is going to be a sweaty  morning  good morning Knuckles are you looking  forward to graduation tomorrow you're  gonna stay to listen to my speech right  maybe I don't know  huh is everything all right you look  super tired  I'm fine I just haven't been getting  enough sleep lately my great-grandfather  Affair started playing this new game  called super hot VR  he's been obsessed with it and has been  playing it all through the night  pretending he's not worthless  Knuckles they are all shining me as I  speak what do I do in this situation  just punch them granddad  it isn't working maybe it's because they  are 20 feet away from me knucklesho I  try and throw in something at them I  guess  stop talking to me  I think I made them mad no matter  pulling out guns Knuckles why didn't you  tell me this game took place in an  American School  oh listen I hate to ask you this but  could you maybe give me a ride on your  bike to the bookstore down the road  the bookstore  I need to replace a textbook because  Sonic took a [ __ ] on it after he thought  I stole one of his diamonds in Minecraft  yeah that'll do it but one of the wheels  on my by cardorn maybe you could take a  cab or something  oh um  or I could walk you down there I guess  gosh are you sure that's a long way to  go you really don't have to it's no big  deal besides I was going down there  after school anyway  okay let's hurry so we make it back in  time for the dance I'll be waiting up  front  hey there lucky boy where you off to in  such a hurry  yeah what you up to  not so much bro hey we still on for  chugging Mountain Dews tonight behind  the bleachers  oh you know what same time every week in  this [ __ ]  still drifting in the waters of  childhood I see  what's that supposed to mean  we're going to be high schooler starting  tomorrow so we are practically grown-ups  are you sure you should be spending your  time drowning away in some gamer poison  and it's not only graduation we have to  think about but the school dances  tonight too  don't you got dates  holy off bro I know what you're trying  to do and it's not going to work I'm not  going to vote for you to be prom King  just because you're my brother that's  right nobody actually cares about who  becomes prompting anyway it's all a show  spoken like a man who's already conceded  defeat I don't blame you let me guess  you still haven't got to [ __ ] date  have you you got to learn to take things  slow my man treat somebody right like  how my sexy huncover boyfriend does me I  can't get a date if I want  right as if you are in the dating scene  all of a sudden you know if it wasn't  for that sad little thing you got for my  ugliesis I would start to think you were  a gay [ __ ] [ __ ]  wait you're not thinking of asking her  out  so what if I am  that's enough bro let the Echidna have  his space  stay in your lane gunky puss and get  your hand off my belly it's almost  touching my boobs  it's all right bartlebby I've got this  one  foreign  do you don't you get your place is the  friend zone and I'll tell you ain't  nobody in the history of middle school  has ever escaped the friend zone nobody  all right Bros break it up we don't need  to use this as an excuse to go all  Gangsta up in this Hood like black  people or Uncle Chuck  you are lucky my bro was here to hold me  and my muscles back knucklehead  otherwise you would be walking away from  here with a set of popped balls  come on bro let's go eat donut holes  [Music]  well I didn't expect it to be so chilly  out already but I guess it's to be  expected what with the holidays right  around the corner and all  you still want to walk you can't always  just borrow my textbook if you want I'll  need it back by science class though  hum well I can't take it if you can  let's go  [Music]  this sucks if my bike hadn't broken down  we'd have been there and back by now  Well it can't be helped still it's nice  to step away and be alone now and again  don't you think  oh not that our friends aren't good  company that's not what I'm trying to  say at all  just say it say it [ __ ] [ __ ] say our  friends suck balls you know it's true  it's just we don't get much time alone  together is what I'm trying to say  you coward  so are you going to the dance tonight  it seems like your brother is aiming to  become prom queen or some [ __ ]  haha can he even do that he's a boy I  wonder who he wants to be prompting I  think we already know who that is though  personally I don't care about any of  that stuff I'm just really stoked to  hang out with everyone  so you're not going with anyone in  particular  well no nobody's asked me  would you maybe want to go with me  [Music]  okay okay yeah that sounds like fun  [Music]  don't go looking at useless crap just  get the textbook entry I can't afford  another darty slip on my record or I'll  get expelled  you're not the boss of me  [Music]  College that's right we'll be graduating  tomorrow and after that we'll be high  school  surely some of us will be heading to  college when that's through  and the ones who don't will find jobs I  wonder how many of us have it all  planned out  or if we'll even be friends anymore when  that time comes  Jared you go right I'll go take the guys  on the left don't let them touch your  balls  Jared what's taking so long I cleared  you a path shoot the damn ball  it's down my mouth I think they want to  get a whiff of my rank butt crack or  some [ __ ] because I left my deterrent at  home  get away from me 12 year olds  fine if you want to test if my crap so  bad I'll let you take all you want  throw it here I'll go for a two-pointer  [Music]  hot diggity dog that was a sick shot  right there manic I don't think anyone  has ever made it to Poynter in the  history of the score before you were the  real deal  what did you expect basketball as my  game  you can't tell because I have an in  wordpass  he now that the match is over want to go  eat some bread and butter me and my paw  grower own wheat on a family farm and  make our own butter by stepping in  cheese curds with our dirty feet  what happened to the sexy Indian chick  that used to be on the Lando Lakes  butter container manic did the white man  steal her land too why do you have that  I thought you said you make your own  butter  oh yeah I do I'm certainly not lying to  make myself look like a better farmer  than I actually am  oh okay  hey Jared look there's your [ __ ] sweet  I was just itching to have someone gag  on my balls it looks like I won't have  to use you after all manic  hey Hill Billy how do you get on your  knees and prepare to swallow some nuts  and maybe poop you if I'm feeling a  little frisky oh yeah babe I didn't know  you had practice today  you brought me a promposal for the dance  you couldn't wait until then to get it  up the ass you naughty girl chooks babe  you didn't have to go through the  trouble I was going to [ __ ] you  regardless even if I had to rape you  oh yeah rude wait that letter isn't for  you who else could it be for besides  your boyfriend you know you are acting  kind of CIS right now [ __ ]  would you look at that the usual suspect  rears its ugly head once again a letter  to my [ __ ] dad you know I was cool  with it when I caught my dad balls deep  in your fat ass inside of the backyard  out house I even let you get away with  making him a Ballade sandwich but a love  letter a man has to draw the line  somewhere  okay  [Music]  what's going on in there  oh [ __ ]  Jared where are you going  you don't see [ __ ]  I don't believe this Meg I knew you were  one of the cooler kids that would spend  your hair up with too much hair tell but  blowing off another student's legs with  a pump action shotgun and then pooping  down her mouth I'm afraid this calls for  drastic for measures I'm expelled no  you're going to have to stay for seven  minutes after class today  but it wasn't me this time I swear what  about the dance  I'm sorry son but I'm afraid a school  dance has no use for bad eggs on the  bright side you're not black you're  green like my [ __ ] after I eat too much  vegetables and I think that's pretty  cool  hmm  okay  [Laughter]  [Music]  why is Bart Levy here he doesn't even go  to this school shutter your mouth [ __ ]  that man is that gets a bowl of pork  looks like it's nearing seven o'clock  what happens at seven o'clock  I told you that's when I'm going to  murder Dr Robotnik  are you serious dude I thought you were  joking about that I don't play games  Trevor I'm a freedom fighter and Batman  stole my childhood  even so Cyrus what makes you think he's  even going to come here for a fight  don't you think he has better things to  do than see your sorry lemon ass not  really but I just sent out a fake email  saying the school is having a massive  pizza party and everyone is invited  there's no way that debuff Lord can pass  on slices of cheese with Crispy  pepperoni  keep your eyes peeled like an orange  your roundness you never know what might  be a trap yeah let's be careful I don't  want to end up in one of those Tick Tock  videos where sexy teenagers make fun of  me for my Australian accent or being  friends with a fat bald man  shut up I'm not fat and don't talk about  my bald head you know I have cancer  wait you have cancer damn I'm I'm sorry  boss when did you find this out I don't  know like two days ago they said I only  have eight months to live just a week  ago I thought I was the perfect specimen  on Earth but my doctor said I'm  overweight and I also found out I'm bald  because I look in a mirror which I  haven't done in the last eight years I  guess because I had such a big mustache  it meant I had a lot of hair on top  apparently there isn't  but that's not important that he needs  some crispy pepperoni sleet can you get  me my baby bib out of the center console  should I get the wheelbarrow out of the  trunk so we can wheel you back  good idea sleet there you go again with  the big brains you see Bingo this is why  he gets paid double of what you get  keep laughing [ __ ] that's still only  two bucks every 19 months  come here sleet I say you earned  yourself a big hug  remind me to buy you some gogurts on the  way home you earned it  they're coming  foreign  now it's telling me to go to the rooftop  with my pants pulled all the way down  [ __ ] so it was a prank after all you're  around Miss shall I take your bid back  to the car  no you fools wait here I will see if  there's a pizza party with my own eyes  hello is anybody here I'm here for the  Super Rad pizza party ignore my mustache  on sparkling ABS I promise I'm nine  years old  oh  don't make any sudden moves fatso  damn it fine go ahead and pull out your  phone and start spanking my ass or  whatever you're going to do but just so  you know I'm very sexy so I doubt you'll  get more than 13 likes  wait a second that hairstyle that looks  like a hairy Balzac  don't I recognize you from somewhere  so you remember that's good years ago  you stole the life of my mother and not  only that but you turned my father into  your sex slave  you got it all wrong I didn't make him a  sex slave I only forced him suck my  balls  every day I have spent my life plotting  for this moment you are not leaving here  Alive Tonight  look yellow boy I can respect your  courage but I have some horrible news  for you I just finished marathoning like  three Jackie Chan movies so I'm kind of  good at karate  big deal I have a [ __ ] gun  you mean the gun I just replaced with a  banana  that's fine I would rather our battle be  personal intimate and man to man like  how you were with my daddy as he  stretched your [ __ ] like bubble gum  I am not gay  [Music]  hey get our masters face out of your  butt  foreign  I see now all this time I must have been  a [ __ ] special ed could because I  thought Sonic the Hedgehog was My One  True rival yet you've been here Cyrus as  my true nemesis  we're like cloud and safety Roth or Zach  Bell and his boyfriend I mean rival  brago  you're right at a glance we appear to be  evenly matched but you know  I have not been fighting at my full  power this whole time  impossible  you forget  I'm a scientist the same as my father  and this unique vest I am wearing right  here is a unique weapon created from the  blueprints left behind by my old man  it amplifies my strength tenfold  it was made to be used against you back  on Mobius but its power was not needed  for Sonic took you out like a [ __ ]  tenfold us and to think you're still  getting yorsha kicked in  you didn't let me finish this vest  amplifies its swearers power only when  it has been turned on  you mean all this time you've been  holding it back  [Music]  only those who accept love and harmony  into their heart can harness this much  power  lesser men like you would be crushed by  the weight  he's not kidding I can feel the power  emanating from his body he's like the  Celtic Guardian  don't just stand there you roundness go  beat his ass  foreign  I can't even touch him he's too fast  oh you're still here  [Music]  Dingo go start the car we were out  sleepy okay I'll go get you some aspirin  from Walgreens  [Music]  times  Trevor what are you doing here you were  right all this time I have been running  away no not running away actually I have  been clinging too tightly to the Past  you're not just not to do anything about  it because I lack the courage  but no more have finally decided to take  control of my own life this time I will  fight  no you won't  huh no it cannot be do my eyes deceive  me it's you the one I see in my  nightmares every night my demon  there's no mistaking it it's the boy who  lives so you finally came to kill me  Trevor here do you want to take my vest  no I need to do this myself and besides  it smells like your sweaty armpits  well then what are we waiting for little  man our final battle begins now  come here  [Applause]  Cyrus help me you don't have the right  to stand up stay down I'm giving you the  discipline your parents never could  don't give up Trevor fight  like hell he will weaklings will always  be weaklings just as the strong will  always get stronger  foreign  [Music]  help me please I'm scared of heights  don't let me fall  you murdered my family in Cold Blood and  now you want Mercy  I didn't have a choice Robotnik told me  to if I went against him I would be dead  right now  Trevor he's defeated to kill him now  will shroud your eyes in darkness we  shouldn't let ourselves become like them  you bring me the pass  [Music]  [Music]  doctor you have escaped death so many  times that I've lost count  this final attack isn't for me but  everyone that you have hurt consider it  your final punishment  [Music]  foreign  what's with the look of sadness my love  you finally got your revenge this should  be a night of Celebration  here have some pizza  I'm sorry I just thought if I could get  rid of Robotnik the sadness would go  away but in the end I still never got my  daddy back  was this Revenge was it really worth it  did somebody say my name  dad is it really you but how can this be  I thought you were roboticized  I was but somehow I'm not anymore  now come give your daddy a small peck on  the cheek  talk about some family bonding  [Music]  Knuckles there you are I was beginning  to think you weren't coming  sorry I'm late went home to change but  um my bike's other wheel popped  so you tried writing it down here on  only one wheel you weirdo  anyway you made it just in time I heard  they're about to announce the winners  yeah before that when you listen there's  something I want to say  huh what is it  well I don't really know how to put this  I guess what I'm trying to say is I've  always  what was that you might want to speak a  little louder I can't hear you over the  crowd  I said that I really like it  you know what just tell me later  and now it's the moment of the night  you've all been waiting for the  unfailing of prime queen and king  Everybody Clap Your Hands line your  clapping cheeks because the pride Queen  for tonight with three eight six volts  is Sonic the Hedgehog will the fat man  step right up and claim his prize  you're not special now hurry up and  climb up there accept your plastic piara  so we can ditch this dusty place and go  to a place for rich people like Olive  Garden  of course a queen is nothing without a  king because everybody knows men are the  only ones who know how to get [ __ ] done  the Prague King who only got two votes  and doesn't even go to this school but  he paid me three trillion dollars  Barnaby Montclair of Dresden  stop it stop it put those cameras away  at least turn the flash off are you  trying to Blind me have you no dignity  stop leave me alone I'm a normal person  just like the rest of you yeah I can't  do you think that's the time  bartlebby bartlebby help they're going  to kill me  make way let my [ __ ] through you  blasted barbarians yeah [ __ ] take my  muscular hand and I will save your life  out of the door I will not ask you to  get open his mouth I want to touch your  lips  Drive damn you drive  [Music]  bark web either throwing rocks  [ __ ] and this is the longest limo in the  world too  yes I have to replace like 2000 Windows  did I say you could take a break no now  get back to pulling pumpkin boy  we still have 23 miles until the nearest  Little Caesars to pick up a hot and  ready Five Dollar Pizza  foreign  so now that that's done what do you want  to do next I still have two hours until  my bedtime  well I have this coupon for Olive Garden  but I was going to use it for myself  maybe we can split it  now I'll just use it for myself  hello can I get a box of spaghetti with  the sauce on the side in a little cup  I like to pour it on top myself and can  I get a Pepsi without ice I have a  coupon but the expiration date says  today does that mean I can still use it  oh okay that's good one moment please I  must consult with my beach boy  [ __ ] do you want anything from Olive  Garden okay  what do you have on the kids menu you  have chicken nugget can you like take  the meatballs out of the spaghetti and  mix in chicken nuggets I'll pay extra  okay we'll do that  [Music]  foreign  [Music]  strong  until I walk awake  [Music]  foreign  [Music]